nfluk.com 2018-06-18

# NFLUK.com | Privacy Policy

Updated as May 21, 2018

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to this website www.nfluk.com (the "Website"). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.

The Website is maintained and operated by NFL International Ltd ("NFL IL"), whose offices are at 30 Panton Street, Leicester Square, London, SW1Y 4AJ. NFL IL is a member of the National Football League and part of the NFL group of companies (the "NFL Family" - as described in Section 4 below) (collectively, "we", "our", or "us"), and if you use this Website your personally identifiable information will be shared among the members of the NFL Family as described below. We have contracted with third parties, including, without limitation, OverTier and Two Circles, to operate certain aspects of the Site, such as the following subscription products: Audio Pass, Game Pass, Game Rewind and Red Zone (collectively, the "Subscription Products").

We are responsible for the information collected via the Website and we may use it for our own purposes, including marketing. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected via the Website; it does not apply to any other information collected or obtained through other means or information collected by the thirty-two individual NFL member clubs (the "Member Clubs").

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [ **enquiries@NFL.com**](mailto:enquiries@NFL.com).  If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request. You may lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your Personal Data infringes applicable law.

NFL IL is the data controller for processing of personal information. When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" or "personal information," we mean information defined as personal data under applicable data protection law. That includes information that identifies or could identify by expending reasonable effort a particular individual, such as your name, street address, email address, or certain online identifiers. When other information, such as a favourite team or player, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this privacy policy.

1.  Types Of Information That May Be Collected

2.  How Information May Be Collected

3.  How We Use The Information Collected

4.  With Whom The Information May Be Shared

5.  Links To Other Websites

6.  Security

7.  Data Retention

8.  Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards

9.  A Special Note For Parents Concerning Privacy

10.  Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy And Notification Of Changes To The Privacy Policy

11.  Correcting/updating personal information

12.  Questions About This Privacy Policy

**1.          TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED**

The following are the types of information we may collect:

Information You Provide Us In the course of using the Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or fax number; unique identifiers, such as your user ID, or user password; demographic information, such as your date of birth or age; and financial information, such as your credit card number or similar information.

Website Usage Information We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website, such as your click-stream data and your IP address. See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.

Email Communications When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation notifying us that you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have selected to receive or not to receive. If you would like to opt-out of receiving such emails, please click on the "unsubscribe" link in the email and follow the instructions.

Information from Other Sources We may receive demographic information about you (e.g., length of residence) from marketing service providers and other third party providers, and use it to provide you with more tailored content and services.

**2.          HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED** We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:

Registration You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, such as newsletters or contests. Your decision to register is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to us and what communications you would like to receive; however, please be advised that many products and services available on the Website require registration and if you elect not to provide such information, you will not be able to take advantage of those products and services.

Contests or Sweepstakes We periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through the Website that will require registration or the submission of personal information. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes (see the rules of each contest for details about how your personal information will be used, including postings to the Website).

Surveys or Voting From time-to-time we may request personally identifiable information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary, and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. At times, you may have to register to vote or to take part in a survey.

Games When you register to play games on our Website, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information.

Tracking Technologies NFL IL and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyse trends, administer the website, track users? movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html

These small bits of code automatically identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Tracking Technologies also let us know how many people visit the Website and where visitors go on the Website. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like how many times a user has been on certain pages. For registered users, cookies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, tracking technologies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Website are based on data obtained from tracking technologies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalise your experience on the Website. Tracking technologies may also allow the Website to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of tracking technologies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookie data at any time. Some areas of the Website, however, may not provide you with a personalised experience if you have disabled the use of tracking technologies. We set out below a more complete description of the tracking technologies used by the Website and the purposes for which they are used.

IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of the Website. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information we obtain from you directly on the Website or any other of our other websites, or from third parties.

Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analysed, this data helps us analyse how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

Transaction Information

If you conduct a financial or other transaction with the Website, such as subscribe to a Subscription Product or other products/services offered on the Website, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and/or financial information. In some instances, we may direct you to a third party vendor site to collect this information from you directly. Even though the collection form may have the look and feel of www.nfluk.com, please be aware you will be giving your information directly to the third-party vendor, and that in some instances such third party vendor's privacy policy will govern the collection of your personal information. Please reference the privacy policies available from these pages for any privacy related concerns.

We and/or our vendor will use this information to complete the financial or other transaction that you have requested, i.e. to deliver the information, products or other services that you request or purchase, to invoice you, and in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. For your protection, financial information is collected and stored through encrypted means.

**3\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED**   The information you provide to us may be used for the following purposes, with the corresponding legal bases:

Purpose of Processing| Primary Legal Basis for Processing  
---|---  
To identify and authenticate you so you may use the Website. | Necessary for the performance of the contract between you and NFL IL and for our legitimate interests.  
To provide you with services or information you have requested or products or services you have ordered, such as subscription plans or other products and services. | Necessary for the performance of the contract between you and NFL IL.  
To communicate with you regarding products or services you have purchased (including tickets and subscriptions) or changes to the Website or the Privacy Policy. | Necessary for the performance of the contract between you and NFL IL and for our legitimate interests.  
To confirm or fulfil an order you have made. | Necessary for the performance of the contract between you and NFL IL.  
To inform you of a prize you may have won. | Necessary for the performance of the contract between you and NFL IL.  
To monitor or improve the use of the Website. | Necessary for our legitimate interests.  
To customise the advertising and content you see. | Necessary for our legitimate interests.  
To monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website. | Necessary for our legitimate interests.  
To send promotional material or special offers relating to the NFL Family, as well as on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties. | Based on your separate consent.  
  
Where required by applicable law, we will procure necessary consents. Where personal information is processed on the basis of consent by our customers, that consent may subsequently be withdrawn at any time (by visiting your account page on the website and using the information deletion function to request that your information be deleted) without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

We use automated decision-making technologies, including profiling, to support our data processing activities. Our automated decision-making capabilities include logic that analyses your preferences based on your usage of the Website and the information we collect. By using this logic, it helps us present you with content and marketing that matches your preferences. For you, this means that your experience of the Website will be more personalised.

**4.          WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED** At times, as described below, we may share your personal information with others for the specified purposes:

·    **Agents:** We employ other businesses (e.g., Two Circles, Inc.), certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, providing the Subscription Products, sending email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Website analysis, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. We may share information with third-parties, such as social networking platforms, so that they may send tailored communications on our behalf via their platforms. These companies may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use or disclose it for other purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.

·    **Aggregate Information:** We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organisations, to help them improve their products and services. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

·    **Opt-in to Receive Third Party Offers:** Throughout the Website you may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers sent from third party(s). Opt-in opportunities will ask you if you would like your personally identifiable information to be shared with such third party(s) as necessary to receive such information or marketing offers. If you do not elect to "opt-in" to having your personally identifiable information shared, your personally identifiable information will not be shared with such third party(s). If you do choose to have your personally identifiable information shared, your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) solely for the purpose of permitting such third party(s) to provide you with such information and marketing offers. Such third party(s) is/are not authorised by us to disclose your personally identifiable information to any other third parties. Please be advised that if you elect to provide your personally identifiable information in response to such third party(s) marketing offers or otherwise, all information you disclose to such third party(s) will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information to such third party(s).

·    **Products or Services Offered in Partnership with Third-Party(s):** Certain products and/or services available on the Website are provided to you in partnership with third party(s) and may require you to disclose personally identifiable information in order to register for and access such products and/or services. Such products and/or services shall identify the third party partners at the point of registration. If you elect to register for such products and/or services your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information in connection with such products and/or services.

·    **Subsidiaries and Affiliates:** We may share your information (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) for the purposes set forth above with all members of the NFL Family, including, without limitation, our subsidiaries and affiliates (e.g., NFL International Ltd, NFL International LLC, NFL International Ltd, NFL Ventures, L.P., and NFL Ventures, Inc.), and any of the Member Clubs where you have indicated a preference (each of whom has its own privacy policy, which is available on each Member Club's respective website).

·    **Third-Party Ad Serving and Audience and Traffic Measurement Services:** We may use a third-party network advertiser to serve the advertisements on the Website or may use a traffic measurement service to analyse the traffic on the Website. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to this Website and other websites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products or websites you might be interested in. Audience and Traffic Measurement Services allow us to collect anonymous traffic and behaviour information from the Website by monitoring anonymous visitor activity. Although advertisers or other companies do not have access to the Website cookies, the Website's advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have your cookies enabled in your browser. Cookies allow third-party advertisers to show you advertisements or content you might be interested in. Note that any images (or any other parts of a web page) served by third parties in association with third-party cookies may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities. Other companies' uses of their cookies are subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Please click here in order to learn more about the information collection practices and "opt-out" procedures of third-party ad servers we may use.

·    **Business Transfers:** In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred, all personally identifiable information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer. You will be notified of such a transfer in accordance with the "Changes to the Policy" section below.

·    **Administrative or Legal Process:** We or others may disclose your personal information to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law, law enforcement agencies, to protect our or third parties' rights, or to protect the rights of other users of the Website.

Some of these parties (for example, many members of the NFL Family) may be located in countries, such as the United States, other than your own, whose privacy and data protection laws may not be equivalent to those in your country of residence. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, including the United States, we apply appropriate safeguards, to protect your information and comply with applicable laws. For example, we implement measures such as standard data protection contractual clauses to ensure that any transferred Personal Data, remains protected and secure. A copy of these clauses can be obtained by emailing enquiries@nfl.com.

**5.          LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES** You should be aware that when you are on the Website you could be directed to other websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Website onto a different website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Website's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to the Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

**6.          DATA SECURITY AND INTEGRITY** The Website incorporates reasonable technical, administrative, and physical measures to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse, interference, unauthorised access, disclosure, destruction and alteration. We also maintain reasonable procedures to help ensure that such data is reliable for its intended use and is accurate, complete and current. Your personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilising encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.

**7.          DATA RETENTION** We will retain your information only for so long as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out above, considering criteria such as applicable rules on statute of limitations, legal requirements and the duration of your use of the Website and receipt of our services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at Enquiries@nfl.com.

**8.          CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS, AND MESSAGE BOARDS** The Website and the NFL Mobile application (?NFL Mobile?) may make chat rooms, forums, commenting and message boards available to you and other users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. In addition, when you post a comment to NFL Mobile, the user name with which you registered for the Website and your current location will be made publicly available on the Website and through NFL Mobile. By using the commenting features of the Website and NFL Mobile, you acknowledge that your user name and location information will be disclosed. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at Enquiries@nfl.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**9.          A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY** The Website is a general audience website. On the Website, we do not currently knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. If, in the future, we collect personally identifiable information from children on the Website, we will do so in compliance with applicable laws. For more information about the privacy practices for our affiliated website, NFLRush.com, which is directed to children, please consult the privacy policy at that website.

The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's website and explore the GetNetWise website to learn more about parental control tools.

**10.          YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY** By using the Website, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on the Website and / or send an email to users who have provided an email address. We will assume that you have given your permission for your information to be used under the terms of the Privacy Policy, as modified, if you do not respond to our email within thirty days or continue to use the Website thirty days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.

**11.          CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION** If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address or post code), or if you no longer desire to have access to the Website, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us. You may request that we do so by emailing us at Enquiries@nfl.com, signing into your online account and making the desired changes, or via mail at: NFLUK.com user information, NFL International, 8th Floor, 30 Panton Street, London, SW1Y 4AJ. We will respond to you without undue delay and at the latest within one month.

**12.          YOUR DATA RIGHTS** You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to object to or request the restriction of processing of your personal information, and to request access to, erasure and portability of your own personal information. Requests should be submitted by contacting us by emailing Enquiries@nfl.com.

**13.          QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, contact Enquiries@nfl.com.

**EU Cookie Policy**

What is a cookie?

Cookies are small, usually randomly encoded, text files that are designed to store basic information (such as visitor preferences). A cookie file is created by the Website you're browsing, and is transmitted and processed by your computer's Web browser software. The resulting file is stored in your Web browser's installation directory or subfolder (cache).

Your Web browser accesses this file when you visit the Website that originally created the cookie. The Web browser uses the information stored in this file to help ease your navigation of the Web site by letting you log in automatically or remembering settings you selected during your earlier visits to the Web site, among many other functions. Cookies cannot be used to identify you personally.

Like many Websites, we use cookies to obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses some of our Web pages.

These pieces of information are used to improve services for you, for example:

  * Enabling a service to recognise your device so you don't have to give the same information several times during one task
  * Recognising that you may already have given a username and password so you don't need to do it for every web page requested
  * Measuring how many people are using services, so they can be made easier to use and there's enough capacity to ensure they are fast

**How do we use them?**

The list below shows what cookies we use on our Website, why, and how long they are programmed to stay on your computer or device.

1) Cookies for Improving Service using Analytics

We use Omniture Site Catalyst to help us measure how many people visit the site and what they are interested in. The information helps us tailor the site better to your requirements.

**URL:**[ **  http://www.nfluk.com**](http://www.nfluk.com/)[ **  http://forum.nfluk.com**](http://forum.nfluk.com/)

The cookies involved in this process are:

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Content Description**

| 

**Purpose**

| 

**Expiration Date**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
s_cc

| 

This cookie is set and read by the JavaScript code to determine if cookies are enabled (simply set to "True")

| 

Help us measure how many people visit the site and what they are interested in. The information helps us tailor the site better to your requirements

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed  
  
s_gpv_pn

| 

Contains the URL of the currently open document (Web page)

| 

Help us measure how many people visit the site and what they are interested in. The information helps us tailor the site better to your requirements

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed  
  
s_getNewRepeat

| 

Determines whether a user on your site is a new visitor or a repeat visitor

| 

Help us measure how many people visit the site and what they are interested in. The information helps us tailor the site better to your requirements

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed  
  
s_sq

| 

This cookie is set and read by the JavaScript code when the ClickMap functionality is enabled; it contains information about the previous link that was clicked on by the user

| 

Help us measure how many people visit the site and what they are interested in. The information helps us tailor the site better to your requirements

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed  
  
s_vi

| 

Unique visitor ID time/date stamp

| 

Help us measure how many people visit the site and what they are interested in. The information helps us tailor the site better to your requirements

| 

This is a persistent cookie  
  
s_sq_session

| 

Randomly encoded session string

| 

Help us measure how many people visit the site and what they are interested in. The information helps us tailor the site better to your requirements

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
2) Cookies for User Accounts and Community Features

We use cookies to maintain an active login session on the Web site, Community, and Forum.

**URL:**  [ **http://www.nfluk.com**](http://www.nfluk.com/)[ **  http://forum.nfluk.com**](http://forum.nfluk.com/)

The cookies involved in this process are: 

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Content Description**

| 

**Purpose**

| 

**Expiration Date**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
gvo_log_value

| 

Determines whether an active user login session exists

| 

To remember your selections that you've already made when looking at information or using a service on our website

| 

This is a persistent cookie  
  
gvo_user_id

| 

Unique visitor login account ID

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
gvo_browsing_lang

| 

Contains the Web browser character encoding (en-US)

| 

To remember your selections that you've already made when looking at information or using a service on our website when the browser is closed

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72  hours of inactivity  
  
SESS_<string>

| 

Randomly encoded session string

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
bbsessionhash

| 

Randomly encoded session string

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
bblastvisit

| 

Time/date stamp in epoch format

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
bblastactivity

| 

Time/date stamp in epoch format

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
bbuserid                         

| 

Unique visitor login account ID

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
bbpassword

| 

Account password in an encrypted format

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
External Links

| 

Randomly encoded session string

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
symphony

| 

Randomly encoded session string

| 

This cookie is required for user login.

| 

This cookie is a session cookie and expires when the browser is closed, user has logged out, or after 72 hours of inactivity  
  
QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of this Website, contact  [ **enquiries@nfl.com**](mailto:enquiries@nfl.com)

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to:

NFL International  
8th Floor  
30 Panton Street  
London  
SW1Y 4AJ  
Attn: Website Privacy Policy  
Ph: +44 (0)20 7534 0030
